{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_7_0CCXRU",
                "player_6_0CCXRU",
                "player_5_0CCXRU",
                "player_3_0CCXRU"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                7,
                6,
                5,
                3
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "pick_up",
                "stand",
                "liedown"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A bald man with glasses, dark complexion, wearing a black turtleneck, suit, and shoes",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    82.213,
                    -656.032,
                    201.897,
                    0,
                    60.52624610109035,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    236.488,
                    -555.537,
                    201.898,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    150.904,
                    -318.64,
                    214.337,
                    0,
                    149.15516245980865,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -212.473,
                    -305.086,
                    211.969,
                    0,
                    -168.29492836470178,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -146.971,
            -260.382,
            227.23
        ],
        "sample_radius": 684.5600916191922
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            198.858,
            -56.242,
            213.117,
            0,
            -108.48374744909925,
            0
        ],
        [
            111.339,
            -1264.557,
            217.383,
            0,
            93.34236079121524,
            0
        ],
        [
            666.046,
            -575.473,
            201.898,
            0,
            169.0295112463329,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_bald_man_in_glasses or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many individuals are in a crouching posture in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many figures are in a standing position?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are observed to be lying down?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many people are holding something?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Among all the individuals present, how many are identified as male?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene do not have a bald head?",
                "answer": "three"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouching",
                    "B. holding something",
                    "C. running",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "B. holding something"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. walking",
                    "C. stand",
                    "D. jumping"
                ],
                "answer": "C. stand"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the deep V-neck top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. liedown",
                    "C. standing",
                    "D. jumping"
                ],
                "answer": "B. liedown"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the back-right of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the front-left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the left of"
            }
        }
    }
}